

Radosław Żuchelkowski

Cybersecurity Specialist/Red Team Specialist/Penetration Tester/Sales Manager/MBA

+48 600 088 722 · radek.zuchelkowski@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am Technical Engineer of Computer Engineering specialty that gave-up his engineering background for sales career. Still not convinced if it was a mistake. With more than 20 years of experience in the area of sales management, working for best SI/IT/SMARTPHONE players on the market, I recently decided to "return to the roots" and complete Red Team Specialist course for Cyber Security professionals (to the courtesy of HackerU/University of Warsaw). It is obvious how sales, especially ever increasing online sales, is closely connected with Cyber Security threats nowadays and it is only a tip of the iceberg called Cyber Security. Personally, I find it very exciting. I am open to positions in Cyber Security field that will harness my sales expertise and/or let me continue to specialize/job profile in Cyber Security field (SIEM solutions, Red Teaming, Pen Testing, Mobile Security, etc.). I am a result oriented, communicative, analytical approach individual. In all my work environments I always tried to bring a dose of humor because I believe it eases the negative effects of operating under stress for a long time.

For more details please refer to Linked-in profile:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/radosław-żuchelkowski-050a80/

EXPERIENCE



Senior Sales/Retail KAM

OPPO

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

- Managed sales of CES account RTV Euro AGD ("Euro-net" Sp. z o.o.)
- Product Group: smartphones, IOT
- Communicated the progress of weekly sales initiatives to internal and external stakeholders
- · Monitored sales and feedback from customers
- · Answered customer queries and concerns to the best of my ability
- · Brought forth a self-motivated attitude
 - Served as an enthusiastic and productive team member

S∧⊗SUNG

Senior Sales/Retail KAM

Samsung Electronics Polska

Aug 2014 - Jan 2021 (6 years 6 months)

- Managed sales of CES account Mediaexpert (TERG S.A.)
- Responsible for Team of 1 Sales Specialist
- Product Group: smartphones, tablets, wearables, accessories
- Helped to increase customer retention by striving to create wonderful customer experiences
- Researched competition and developed strategies to stand out as a company against competitors

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych zawartych w mojej ofercie pracy dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji.

Soft Skills

Communication Skills
Ability to Work Under Pressure
Ability to Work in a Team
Leadership
Good team player
Fast Learner

Hobbies

Skiing, cybersecurity, motorcycles, hiking, rock climbing, MTB, road cycling

Languages

English German C1

Courses

Negotiations at McHayes&StewardGroup 08/2012—08/2012

Financial Controlling for Salesman at McHayes&StewardGroup 09/2012—09/2012

MS Excel - Advanced Course/Advanced MS Excel Tools at Imperium Szkoleniowe 06/2015-06/2015

The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People at Franklin Covey

04/2011-04/2011



Sales Manager (B2C Reseller)

Samsung Electronics Polska

Feb 2011 - Aug 2014 (3 years 7 months)

- Managed B2C Reseller Channel (S/M computer re-seller shops)
- · Responsibility for Team of 3 Sales Specialists
- Product Group: notebooks, monitors, printers
- · Served as a successful team leader, collaborating with sales team members to identify growth opportunities and develop strategies to seize them



Retail Account Executive

Acer

Apr 2009 - Jan 2011 (1 year 10 months)

- Managed sales of CES account Mediamarkt (Media Saturn Holding Polska Sp. z o.o.)
- Product Group: notebooks/netbooks, PC's, monitors
- · Maintained and managed client relationships
- · Answered customer queries and concerns to the best of my ability
- · Monitored sales and feedback from customers



Channel Sales Manager (notebooks)

LG Electronics

Feb 2005 - Feb 2009 (4 years 1 month)

- · Coordinated all sales channels (resellers, CES) to achieve overall notebook sales target
- · Cooperated with distributors and dealers (ABC Data, Action, Pronox, Incom, NTT, Komputronik, etc.)
- · Cooperated with retail chains (Media-Saturn, Avans, Mediaexpert, Mix, Domator, etc.)
- Created and introduced promotion marketing plans to achieve quarterly sales target (demo programsfor resellers, promotions, motivational programs for distributors, dedicated sales programs for resellers)
- Set and executed monthly sales targets (distributors)
- Cooperated with marketing department in terms of ATL/BTL activities (web site product contents, press ads, product placement, tests, product catalog, etc.)
- Prepared product trainings and presentations for all sales channels
- · Recruited and manages sales promoters team of 11 persons

EDUCATION



University of Warsaw/HackerU

RED TEAM SPECIALIST, Certified Cybersecurity Specialist

Nov 2021 - Jun 2022, Warsaw, Poland



W Walsh College

MBA

1999 - 2001, Troy MI, USA



West Pomeranian University of Technology in Szczecin

1993 - 1998, Szczecin, Poland

HARD SKILLS IN DETAIL

LINUX FUNDAMENTALS

Introduction to Linux, Users, Groups&Permissions, Network Configuration & Package Management, Configuring Services

WINDOWS SERVER 2016

Creating an Organization, Active Directory Management, Working with Services DHCP & DNS, GPO Management

BYPASSING THE PERIMETER

WireShark, MITM, OSINT&Social Engineering, Network Scanning, Password Cracking, MetaSploit & Known CVEs, Wi-Fi Attacks, Web Anonymity

SIEM & SOC

SIEM & SOC Introduction, End-Point Protection, Network Protection & Prevention, Log Generation & Collection, SIEM Solutions, IOC & Malwares, Windows Live & Offline Analysis, Memory Analysis, Basic Static Analysis, Basic Dynamic Analysis

CROSS PLATFORM ELEVATION OF PRIVILEGES

Windows Local Privilege Escalation, Windows Post Exploitation & Credentials Dumping (Mimikatz), Linux Local PE & Post Exploitation, Linux Automated Tasks & Permission Misconfiguration, Common Exploits & Buffer Overflow, Unquoted Services & DLL Hijacking

ADVANCED INFRASTRUCTURE

Enumerating an Organization, Lateral Movement, Obfuscation Techniques,
Office Exploitation, Exploiting Services within an organization, SMB Relay & Responder, PowerShell as a
Weapon, Reverse Shells & Tunneling, Kerberoasting & Pass the Ticket & Module Review

PYTHON FOR HACKING

Introduction to Python, Data Types & Loops, Functions & Code Handling, File System & Error Handling, Web Communication, Sockets Fundamentals, Protocols Communication, Scapy & Network Scanning

WEB FUNDAMENTALS

Introduction to HTML, CSS Fundamentals, JavaScript Fundamentals, Building Web Pages, Advanced JavaScript, Introduction to Server-Side

WEB APPLICATION PENETRATION TESTING

Web Technologies, PHP Vulnreabilities&OWASP Top 10, Burp & ZAP, XSS, Database Management, SQL Injection, Advanced SQL Injection, NoSQL Injection, CSRF & Broken Authentication, XXE & SSRF, LFI/RFI to RCE & WordPress Hacking, PT Flow&Reporting and Vulnerabilities Scanning

MOBILE SECURITY

Introduction to Android, Android Programming, Android Reversing, Android Traffic Analysis, SSL Pinning, Android Malwares & Run Time Debugging, Static & Dynamic Investigation Frameworks, iOS Security